This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is sight!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford to rescue his brother Ace.
He breaks into the plaza and eventually makes his way to the scaffold.
There, with some unexpected help from an old enemy,
Luffy finally frees Ace.
Then, the brothers begin their escape as Whitebeard gives his sons a final order.
Make no mistake! I'm a relic of a bygone era.
Long have I sailed.
But no ship can carry me into the new age.
Let's finally put an end to this.
The power that can burn even fire.
Akainu's Ruthless Pursuit.
The Marineford's falling apart!
Somebody stop Whitebeard!
Damn! At this rate, he's gonna bring down the whole island!
We came here as a family! We should leave as one too!
Yeah! Pops, come with us!
You mean to disobey your captain's order?
I told you fools to get away!
Pops, no!
All right! This might be our only chance!
Hit Whitebeard with all you've got!
I won't do it!
Hey, come on, we're better off doing what Pops says.
Are you crazy? Pops is our father!
I won't leave him here to die!
Let go!
Don't be stupid!
Do you think any of us want to leave Pops behind?
Move!
Bickering about your own petty feelings at a time like this,
that's the kind of stuff Pops wouldn't stand for!
Can't you see that he's trying to do what's best for us?
Sorry.
Everyone get back on the ships!
Hey, Ace!
Come on! Hurry it up! We're about to take off!
Commander Marco, let's head back!
Pops...
You completely ruined the Navy's plan!
Die!
Don't kill me!
I just want to leave this disaster!
You don't have to do this!
Sheen your sword!
What the...?
My exquisite wax shell is impenacrable!
You will need more than a cheap blade to pierce this carapace!
Dammit! More devil fruit powers!
Figures!
No wonder he was able to protect Fire Fist Ace on the scaffold!
He even blocked Fleet Admiral Shingoku's attack!
Oh, uh...
Well, I wouldn't say I'm that powerful.
My skill set is better suited for the arts.
Thank you for your time!
Time to mute!
My fear! Unreal! He oughta be dead!
What's it gonna take to put this guy away?!
Go away!
She no longer has to worry about saving Fire Fist Ace.
Admiral, sir?
So long as his men can escape, he'll sink Marineford and all of us with it.
He's prepared to die. I've no doubt.
Vice Admiral Garp! You okay?
Whitebeard thinks our era is over?
Yeah, the old man is probably right.
We still don't know what happened to Whitebeard!
What about his allies? Did he really sell them out or what?
This block out's getting ridiculous!
How long will we have to wait?
If that stupid clown didn't block our view with that fat head of his,
then maybe we'd have a clue what was actually going on!
Is that who I think it is?
Can it really be the renowned pirate Captain Buggy?
Huh?
I'm sorry, did someone say my name?
Weird. So was he trying to tell us something?
Perfect. How am I supposed to write a story on the battle now?
What's wrong with their snails? We don't go it all day!
Really?
That piece of crap is still hiding in his shell?
Come on! Get back out here, Mr. Snail!
We still need your help! Captain Buggy's ready to defeat Whitebeard!
Don't they realize what they're saying?
Yeah, Whitebeard's wounded, but he's tearing down buildings!
Just look at the bastard!
Why'd I have to go and say I'd beat him?
These morons believe anything you tell them!
It's their fault for feeding my ego! I can't help it!
Lure it out! We gotta showcase Captain Buggy's awesomeness for the entire world to see!
Bring it over here! I'll just smash the shell open!
Yeah! One strong pound ought to do it!
No, stick your hand in there and yank!
Let's soak it in salt water! Snails love that, right?
Good idea! Let's do it!
Quit messing with the poor thing, you bulls!
Huh?
Just think about it. It's not like he wants to be here slaving away from the Navy getting stuck in their battles and beaten up by guys like us.
He's just trying to do his job in difficult times!
Filming a war like this has gotta be traumatic, so relax and cut him some slack!
No! How will you broadcast your plan? The Captain Buggy beats Whitebeard senseless as the entire world is watching live plan!
Yeah, isn't that what you wanted? To stick it to the Navy and Whitebeard to prove that you're king of the pirates?
I'm disappointed! Seriously, boss!
Good grief! Sure they're loyal and stupid, but they're also a bunch of hard-ass prisoners who are locked up and impelled down!
I better not piss them off too much!
The transponder snail came out on his own!
What? Is he... is he crying?
It's a miracle! He must have been touched by Captain Buggy's kind words!
Captain Buggy's compassion isn't lost on even the simplest of creatures! He's truly amazing!
We're flattered to be serving such an inspiring leader! Captain Buggy was meant to conquer this world!
Now, stupidest gargle! Why couldn't he just stay in his shell? Are you trying to get Whitebeard to kill me? Thanks, snail!
Okay, let's try again!
Start by making a declaration to conquer the world, whenever you're ready!
Alright, you got this!
Cue smoke! Lights are ready!
Start rolling, you guys!
Well, crap! No backing out now! Here goes nothing, I guess!
Right! Come on! We're starting the broadcast! And make sure you capture the moment that I kill Whitebeard!
Cause that's totally gonna happen!
Hey! Look!
It's back!
But what's going on? I can't make out anything through that smoke!
So did the Navy beat the pirates? Whitebeard? And Ace?
Uh, no!
Transponder snail! Go down a little!
No!
Why, hello everybody! Time for Captain Buggy!
Whoa!
This guy again?
Get to the sea! Now!
Hurry up and get on the ships! We gotta make it back to the new world and fast!
Don't let them get away! Kill as many pirates as you can!
I'm the only pirate you should be worrying about!
Commander Joseph!
He's in pretty bad shape, but I think he can make it!
First, we gotta get him out of here to safety! Everyone lift!
Hey, Pleinheim! Get over here! On the double!
Hurry, straw boy! It's time to make an exit! On the double!
Ace, let's go! The old guy made up his mind!
The old guy made up his mind!
I know... this is it!
Back off, you bastard!
You bastard!
The time for words has passed, my son!
But tell me one last thing.
Are you happy to have this old fool as your father?
You got some fight left.
Look, I'm not going to kill you today, all right?
Don't fight it. You're too valuable to die in a place like this.
Run wild with us and our flag will be yours.
And I will call you my son.
Of course, Dad!
I will call you my son.
Hey, what happened?
The scaffold was destroyed.
They're in the plaza.
Was Fire Fist Ace executed?
Please say something.
Shift the camera to Whitebeard.
I'm Captain Buggy, a legend.
Tell us, Captain Buggy the Clown.
Is it true you're going to be your fellow legend, Captain Whitebeard?
And will you loudly proclaim your stake as one of the four emperors by carrying the severed head of your victim?
I'm Captain Buggy, a legend.
Hey, say something else.
They got that part already to change it up a little.
Enough with Buggy.
Show us what's happening at Marineford.
Yeah!
Come on.
Who cares about this weirdo?
Get him out of the way.
Okay, use that filter.
Nice!
There he is.
What's he doing now?
Out there!
We can't see!
Keep it up!
We're almost there!
Ace!
Loopy!
Stay in front!
Huh?
They're specifically targeting you two!
We cannot let the old man waste his life!
He will not fall in vain!
Farewell.
We've stolen the Navy ship!
Hop aboard!
Do they really think they stand a chance of escaping?
How naive.
Admiral Sakazaki!
Move aside.
I'll handle this.
Never mind that.
Just don't stop running until you reach the ship.
As soon as they rescued Firefist Ace, they fled.
What a cowardly crew.
Just like their washed-up captain.
What?
He's trying to get you riled up!
Don't listen!
Keep it moving!
Don't fall into his trap, you hear me?
Yeah.
That old man, huh?
Some captain he is.
It's not your fault.
That's just Whitebeard.
A washed-up failure.
Ace!
A failure?
Take it back, or else.
Ace!
No!
Don't!
Just keep moving!
He can say whatever he wants.
Let's go!
No one gets away with Mocking Pops.
Stop!
Take it back.
It's not an insult.
It's the truth.
Let me tell you a story.
Your father conquered the Grand Line, something no other pirate has ever accomplished.
After that, he opened the door to the Great Pirate Era by sacrificing his own life.
I hate to say it being a Navy Admiral, but he was King of the Pirates, no question.
Keeping all that in mind, Whitebeard has failed.
His lack of ambition meant he'd never be king of anything but you simple-minded cronies.
Once he brainwashed enough of you into doing his dirty work, he got lazy.
Every now and then you'll find someone who paints him as a peacekeeper.
Start trouble here and Whitebeard will come running, they say.
Ha!
Empty post to keep idiots like you fearful.
You call him hero when he's nothing but a coward.
When Gold Roger was around, Whitebeard always had second billing.
Yet even after Roger's death, he couldn't become king.
So there it is.
The tale of your father's whipping boy.
The great failure, Whitebeard.
Soon enough, he'll be dead.
And no one will remember him.
I can't help but feel sorry for the man.
And all you punks call him your pops.
Did you make this fake family to humor him or are you just as deluded?
Shut it.
He sailed the seas for years, couldn't amount to anything, amassed an army of losers,
and in the end was even stabbed by one of his own sons who put more stock in my word than his own.
And still, he'll die to protect that man.
Have you ever heard of a more pathetic life?
That's enough!
Leave him!
Run!
Ace!
You're wrong.
There's nothing fake about the family he gave us.
But I wouldn't expect a heartless bastard like you to appreciate that.
Like I said, he convinced you, Punx, you meant something to the world.
But your kind doesn't deserve a halt.
You deserve the gallows.
You can it!
You know it's true.
You'll all die as failures.
And Whitebeard's nothing but a lonely old fool.
Whitebeard is the greatest pirate who ever lived, you hear me?
You don't know anything about the man who saved my life!
Get away from the base!
This is his era!
Don't you forget it!
Your pops will end up the same as you, boy.
Dead and by my hand!
How?
Did he burn him?
Thanks to your Logia-type fruit, you're not used to being hurt.
It's made you too cocky.
You may be made of fire, but my magma burns even hotter than that.
Just like Whitebeard.
Second rate to the bitter end.
Yes!
Luffy, stay out of harm's way!
You're in no condition to battle!
Jesus!
Please just be regard!
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, and Dragon the Revolutionary.
To think that the two of you were adopted brothers all these years.
What a victory it be to end both bloodlines.
Everyone else can escape.
The two of you are the only targets I'm after.
Say goodbye.
Pwish!
Opie!
Which gods get the stars together.
แRC accompanied by by the various people.
It has been spiritual beings and time to increase the chances combine with the Kes 아 2050s.
It can blend perfectly quickly and uninkles.
Experience.
This is definitely a VIVRA card, but there's something I neglected to tell you before.
The life force of the owner is also reflected on the paper.
Does this belong to someone close to you?
Yeah! It's my big brother's!
Now you hang on to that, always.
That scrap of paper is going to reunite us someday.
Ace protects his brother from Aka-Inu, but suffers a mortal blow in the process.
Jinbei and the Whitebeard Pirates rush to his aid, but soon realize he is far beyond help.
As Ace takes his final breaths, he gives a heartfelt message to his comrades.
On the next One Piece, looking for the answer, Firefist Ace dies on the battlefield.
I'm going to be king of the pirates!